So hello guys, how are you all?  Welcome to
our second blog.  Thank you so much for all the love you've given to Vogue.
I did
not expect this much.  And with that motivation, today I am
shooting my second vlog.  So guys,
I just woke up.  I am drinking egg milk right now.
And guys, it is my habit to read books etc. in the morning.  I
mean, I am not a student, I have already
completed my school studies.  Now
look at this, this is Autobiography of a Yogi.
So brother, I was just reading this and your
sister-in-law is preparing to go to the bank.
I even told him that let's go somewhere today.  It's the
weekend but she's saying it's
important to go to the bank.  Come a little
early.
Pooja,
yes sir.
What are you doing?  Won't you agree without going to the
bank?
I told you it is necessary.  There is a lot of work today, I will have to
walk a lot.
What are you preparing?
Yes, I am just putting the stuff in.
What kind of book is this?
This is my diary.
Get shut up.  So bank work
is [ __ ] for you.  [laughs]
Guys, the bank people must be watching this video too
[laughs] So, look at Pooja and see
how bank work looks like.   I had to
show this a little.   I have
shown this now.   No no, let's
stop it.  Okay, I am not doing it.
Ok.  Then you come quickly.  Do one thing.
Ok.  Otherwise I will come to pick you up soon.
Ok.
Come to me early today.  I
will try to get free soon.  I will give.
So guys, your sister-in-law is getting ready
for the bank right now.  And see you guys.  So guys,
your sister-in-law has gone to the bank.  Now
I will go downstairs and eat something,
brother.
So guys, my sister is at home.
And look my nephew is
doing his holiday homework.
What is Red doing here?
What is Oye doing?   doing.   Are you
working?   Ca
n't see it.
Show.
What is this?
Worksheet
worksheet
2 plus three tell me.
So guys, whoever has got such holiday homework
during summer vacations,
please do let us know by commenting.  So guys, this holiday
homework is going on here.  Let's go and see
what mom is doing in the kitchen, it is rainy
season today.  So I think Bhaiya is
making something special.  Mummy, what are you making
?
Pakodas.   Are
you making pakoras?
So guys, look,
we are making all types of pakodas like chilli, paneer, cabbage, onion etc.
So guys, I was drinking tea here and
didi found out something
about me.  [laughter] What has brother Abhi done?
Cheating Curry.   I have
cheated.
Where is the curry from?
Why did you cheat?  It's fun.
Cheating is fun.  [laughter] It's
fun.
So what Guy is saying is that cheating is
fun.  Brother, don't do anything like that.  You
guys will also explain to him that cheating is
not a good thing.  Don't do it like this son, do
n't cheat.  So guys,
before going out for a trip, we are going to do some shopping
in the market.  My sister was insisting that she should
go to the market and do some shopping.  Do you want to do any
shopping?
You have crores.   You want to get
rid of ₹1 crore, right?  I have to
spend some money.
Yes.  So Guys currently has
₹1 crore.
Abhi has ₹1 crore.  Where are you
going out in this heat?
[Music]
Who gave one crore?
Nana did.  Nana has not given us
one crore till date.
[MUSIC] Okay.  Bye.
Go and do some shopping.
So guys, I had dropped my sister and mother to the market
with me and by then your
sister-in-law will also be free from the bank and
after that brother, we will go for a walk in Delhi side,
there sister-in-law, brother etc. are all waiting for us, so guys, just now
I was standing here
and my subscribers have come here,
hello,
like it brother, subscribe brother,
how are you all,
fine brother, you tell me, that's
fine, okay, bye guys,
okay [Music]
So brothers, we have just come home and
look, it is still drizzling,
brother.  Now let's get ready quickly
and leave from here.  So guys, I am
ready.  Now let's go downstairs brother.
Brother, your sister-in-law has come.  You have
already come.   Yes,
you are late.  Let us go.
And what is this guy doing?
You will drive the car yourself.   He is
saying that I will drive and take you
today.  Okay
brother, today my nephew will drive the car himself.
[laughs] I have
n't even got the license yet, brother.
How will you manage at such a young age?
Will drive Thar today.
Yes
sister, I taught him driving very quickly.
And what else should I teach you in childhood?  [laughter]
Okay, brother.  Now move aside.  It was a lot of
fun.  Ambulatory.  So guys, now we have
left for Delhi side.  Where will
we go today?
Delhi.   To
do what?   To have
fun.  Tell me what fun you will have?
Go to the trampoline.
I will not take you to the trampoline.   Don't
lie, don't lie too much in the vlog.
[laughs]
Dude, he's saying don't lie too much on Vlog.
[Music]
So guys, I've just challenged Abhi to be
absolutely silent for 5 minutes.
This has been said since then.  Otherwise the trampline will not be
taken.  So now look how he is
sitting with his hand on his mouth.  Yes brother,
now he will not ask me to buy this trampoline equipment.
[Music]
So the guys are home.  The luggage etc. has been
unloaded here.  I have to
park the car and come back now.  There is no space here ahead
brother.  So guys, this is the problem in Delhi,
brother, of parking.  Parking is very difficult to find.
So brother, I will
look for some space ahead and park there.
So guys, I couldn't find space anywhere else, so I had to
park my car here.  And look, this had to be applied with great care
[laughs]
so that the car could pass through there.
[screaming sound]
So the guys are home and let's see
what brother and sister-in-law are cooking.  Hey,
both of them are talking here.
Hello sister-in-law, how are you?
Good.  How are you?
I'm absolutely fine.  So you have invited us today, so are you
feeding us something
today?
This is white sauce pasta.
Oh wow, show me.   It is being
prepared now, which means the curd white sauce is ready.
Yes.
And this is garlic bread.  This garlic butter
is ready.  Mushroom momos are being made in this.
Brother and sister-in-law have prepared a complete Chinese setup.
Italian sorry.
So guys, this macaroni pasta is being prepared.
You will feel hungry just by looking at it.  Oh
drama, oh drama
brother, he has gone mad after eating pasta, he is addicted to
his pasta [laughs]
So guys, the garlic bread has just arrived and
Tai ji has also come [laughs]
Hello, say hello to everyone,
whom should you eat brother, she has
come for the garlic bread, Tai ji had
not come earlier [laughs]
I will just talk to the stall owners, we will get
your stall opened downstairs.  [laughs]
Brother Pooja, your sister-in-law is also learning.   Let's
see what she will make after going home.
Brother, our brother has also come.  So brother, everyone had
eaten and drank.  Now all the brothers are going to the gaming area.
Where you will find trampolines and
many more games.  So look
how happy everyone is.  So the guys have
left the house.  And brother,
we will reach our destination in just 15-20 minutes.
Look how everything is packed in the car.
Where is Ash?  Aash here it is
hey cue two
I am also going to the play area hello
what a thing wow what a thing
what a thing so guys have
come to the play area
brother cartoon planet
[music]
so guys have come to the play area
our entire cartoony planet where Abhi
and Nitara will go to play.
Look guys, I've worn the band.  Do you also want to
go?
Yes, I will still go.  Isn't it?
Okay guys, right now sister-in-law, brother, sister etc. are
all waiting there.  And brother, I and
your sister-in-law have come inside because
your sister-in-law was insisting that she wanted to
play here.
Where do I have to go?
Where do you want to go?
So look at this brother.
Both the children are playing here.
Look here now son, I am enjoying it.
Nithara
oy
oy oy oy they are making
each other fall.
Accident happened.
What will you play?
We will also jump with them.   It is not
allowed like this.  So guys, I don't know
where your sister-in-law has gone.
I am searching everywhere.  Hey, she is sitting.
What are you doing?   Guys,
your sister-in-law is playing pano here in the player.
Wow, I should
play it completely for you.
Tell me what can you play?   You are a
hero,
you are a hero.
Let's put it.
Brother, your sister-in-law hit me on the head.  What kind of
fun are you looking for?
I came and I am having a
lot of fun.
This is a place for children to play.
Someone will interrupt.  Yes, they are children.
[MUSIC]
Easy, easy.  Wow
guys, there are two cars parked here.  But
both of them have to fight on the same car.  Now they have been
told that there are two cars.  Sit in the other one.   Lets go.
Drive, drive.
Hey brother, why are you falling and roaming around here?
[Music]
Pooja, look, he's sitting there in the back.  Brother,
sister-in-law etc. all do the same work.  They
scare them away from here.
[music]
[laughter]
Trying to hide Nitara in that drum right now.  I hid it.
Now brother, I will tell him to find Nitara and
bring her.
Find the now.
Hey, did you already know this?  [laughter]
So guys, look, it's going inside it.
Y has come.
So guys, the kids will keep playing here.
Brother, I don't understand what else to do here
?  So we sit outside with our brothers and sisters.  Go out to the
restaurant.
Yes, let's play this here comfortably.
Brother, look, we have come to the party.
We have thrown a birthday party.
Why are you lying to us?  Who will invite the
guys to the party?  We are here to
feed the children.  Tell me whose party it is.
Tell the child's name.
Aadhya and Aadhya.
Adhya.  Aadhya and Aadhya [laughs]
too
[music]
So Abhisha Bheem is
insisting on eating French fries.
So guys, we had decided that
brother would eat something nice outside in the evening and sister-in-law
made rajma rice.  Someone please come guys,
sister-in-law will make rajma rice.
You were also saying that you
make one and you had said that you
make the best one.  She is telling me that
I did not say anything, I said a
lot [laughs]
and
brother in law both are liars
and brother in law is coming at night so
dinner has to be made for son in law,
you did not say anything spicy about snacks outside, these
are spicy peri peri fries guys [laughs]
brother I told my sister to
sprinkle this in a little synthetic way and see
what she is doing, see
guys see how she is doing it with her hands.
So guys, now we have come back after playing these games
in an hour.  Now look how hungry they are.
Take this and
feed them all fries.
I have made this priya, guys.
What happened now, sister-in-law?  [laughter]
So guys, we've had our meal.  The children have
also eaten it.  Now brother, let's go somewhere else.
Brother will tell you where to go.
Now we will go to Cafe Amdam.  And we
will drink tea there.
[laughter]
Brother, how is he saying this brother?  This [laughs]
clip looked very strange brother.
What happened brother?  [laughter]
[laughter]
You're done, brother.  Churna.
So the guys are just leaving here.
Come on, come on.   Let us go.
[Music]
So this is Guys, the cafe my brother was telling me about.
[MUSIC]
So the guys have their drinks.
This is some mango.  Nice one.  How does it
look?
This is not our house to do water-masala
[laughter] You are
so scared, come let
me look at your side,
then you will be saved [music]
brother, this is not for eating, the guys are just
plucking leaves, they have
sat down from there [music]
so guys, you have already eaten, drank, played, jumped and done everything, you bastard,
why did you make the light [laughter]
so guys, now we are going towards the house, so guys, we have reached
home and brother, one more
member of ours has come, hello ji, Jai Shree
and why did these children start crying, did you start crying
[crying sound]
I told you so many times to do it
slowly, only
one [crying sound]
what are you saying brother, children get hurt
brother, they are
crying brother, they have
played a lot the whole day, they had a lot of fun
brother, it is time to cry after seeing them, so guys,
look at this brother, I was feeling sleepy
and these children are not letting me live,
look at this
brother, I was tired after roaming around the whole day, I was
thinking of sleeping and
Bhabhi Bhabhi's energy never ends.   She has just
brought this string.  And brother,
such a big DJ is kept here.  To show Bhabhi
[laughs]
Bhabhi is saying that no one has to sleep.
Everyone has to enjoy here.
Watch Now Party Online
Watch Now.
Party online
Bhabhi will dance.  [laughter]
[music] [song voice]
Rahale
Nain [music] Done Nain Done Nain, husband
for Sa, husband for Sa,
husband
what's the matter brother, tell me brother
brother is saying that today I will make
sister and brother-in-law fight,
tell me brother, tell me now
[laughter]
why are you taking tension, what happened is on
your side [laughter]
this is what happened
Bhabhi Bhabhi is so keen on giving content in the ongoing vlog
Bhabhi [laughter]
yes give me water guys
now some private things are going to happen that's why I have to
end the vlog here
if you liked the video then like,
share, subscribe
thank you guys meet you in next vlog